What are we gonna do?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
Where'd you go?
What's that? What was that?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
That was the biggest surprise of all!
Hello everyone, I'm Marino Kasaka of Katasaka-saka 46. I'm going to do my own project this time, and the project is...
This time I'm going to do a project of mine, and the project is a series of surprises by Kamurafo.
The reason why I'm doing this project is because in our show "Sukogari ga Sakurazaka", we have a show called "Sukogari ga Sakurazaka".
I'm going to surprise Kamrafo for a week.
I thought of a samonail and it was adopted, so I'm thinking of doing all kinds of surprises.
Today is the day of the recording of "Sukosoku," and I'm going to make a lot of surprises with the help of the Sukosoku staff.
I'm going to go now.
I'd like to send a message to Hono-chan that I'm going to do a surprise today.
The content is, "Dear Hono-chan, today's show is going to be a bit of a surprise.
I'd like to tell you to be careful.
I'll send it to you now.
It's the video of étude below.
Hey, jeden.
What's wrong?
Marino-chan surprised me.
Marino-chan.
Did it start?
It's started.
Poor girl.
By the way, does that mean you'll do it normally?
You mean, like normal?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm not gonna do it.
Are you sure? Marino...
I'm tired, too.
What did you call out to him for?
Someone who doesn't belong here.
Next episode's preview
Thank you for watching.
Please.
Please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
While I'm calling the members for a Youtube meeting,
Yes.
What is it now?
It's like I'm telling everyone where I want to go and what I want to do.
Now, just for the record.
Yes.
Some of them are talking about going to Hiraparu.
To Hira Par, for sure.
I'm making it an artist now.
Thank you very much.
I've put in a picture.
Oh, yes.
Open it up for me.
Thank you very much.
Mmm.
I'm sorry.
Thank you if you don't mind.
Thank you if you don't mind, I'm a fan of Shake 'n Cream.
I'm glad you like Shake Cream. Are you okay?
Yeah, nothing.
I'll just have one.
I'm good with one.
That's right.
You can point me towards my parents' house or something.
If there's any other places you want to go.
I'd be happy to hear all about it, and we can plan it for later.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
In Osaka?
Even if it's not in Osaka.
Even if it's not?
I'll take advantage of this opportunity.
I'd like to go to the hot springs with the Onsen Club.
There are four of us.
I'd like to go.
And?
We'll eat and walk around.
And eat in the room.
Is that right?
We can all hang out together.
Staying over or what?
Staying overnight
I'm going to spend YouTube money because I'm going to be there.
I want to do what I want to do
I want to travel
It's hard to find time off.
So if it's as a job, I'd like to do it.
I thought maybe we can make time for each other.
We can have vacations together.
And money.
Money.
Yeah.
Huh.
Ahh!
Ahh! Ahh!
Wear.
ME.
But it was so obvious.
But the cracker didn't dampen me as much as I thought it would.
I noticed the move cushion and Honno was a little hesitant to sit on it.
Honnochan was a little hesitant to sit on the cushion.
But the staff at the meeting kept talking about it, which was really interesting.
Well, I'm off to the next trick!
When Honachan comes out now
I'm going to sound the collacker.
Boom!
Good night.
Is it bad?
I don't know.
It's been a long time in some places.
It's piled up.
I tried to surprise you today, but it was too obvious.
But it was so obvious that I couldn't do it on my own.
So I called in three helpers.
Keep up the good work. Good luck.
Thank you.
This is my last chance before Hono-chan leaves, so I'll do my best.
Let's do our best. Let's do our best.
I want to surprise you.
She's hiding in a pretty spot.
It's obvious from her cheeks.
She's hiding straight ahead.
The moment you step in, you'll see me like this.
Are you practicing your footsteps?
I never make footsteps.
Really? - Yeah.
She's good.
I can get close.
She's gonna move like she doesn't know you're there, so, you know...
That's true.
She's got presence.
She's got a presence.
We don't have to get too close.
It's like, if it's loud enough, it's like, "Oh, my God, it's so loud.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
So you can use the mask.
Yeah, Shubri.
I want to be ready for you, too.
I'll be here soon.
I'll do my best.
Good luck with that.
I want to make sure the dossier is a success.
I'll do my best.
I'm not going to leave it to you.
What are you doing?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
Thank you for your hard work.
What are you doing waiting in the tent?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
They're coming.
I'll see if he's coming.
But бы...
Oh!
Oh, my God!
That was amazing!
That's what I'm talking about!
Ha-ha-ha!
That was amazing!
That feels great!
That's great!
That was amazing!
Oh, my gosh!
It's really not what I had in mind.
Oh, yeah?
We're going to have a dummy arena.
I'm going to leave the arena as a dummy, just for the sake of clarity.
The pine trees are behind it.
Surprise me.
And then Yuchan does it in the car.
in the car.
But Hono was looking in Matsu's direction the whole time.
I couldn't see it.
You couldn't see it?
Yes!
I can hear something.
I know I shouldn't, but...
Oh, my God!
I couldn't hit it!
I couldn't hit it.
That was the most amazing thing I've ever heard.
Oh, my God!
You did a great thing in a great place.
Look at this!
Party! Party! Party!
Party!
Thank you.
You scared the shit out of me!
I'm so glad you were surprised.
Marina was the best.
You're doing great!
Thank you!
You scared me.
As expected
That's what I'm talking about.
As one would expect.
As expected...
You must be a big fan!
I was so nervous that my heart was racing.
But at the end...
I'm so happy!
I'm so relieved!
You got me!
I'm down!
I've been hit!
So...
I'll be here all day long.
Kilo Ishikohime.
How was it?
Well, to be honest, I guessed it all.
But I was a little surprised at the end.
I was really surprised.
You're going to be able to track him down?
Yes!
I'm going to stop! We're gonna stop!
I'm scared!
I'm so scared.
I'm so scared at the moment.
It's really...
It's so powerful!
Even I'm screaming.
That's what you do.
I was really surprised.
What other surprises do you have in store for the members?
Did anyone else?
Who?
Honestly, I think everyone would guess.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Cannon knows it's a staff member.
He's so oblivious.
But Onuma?
Yes, of course.
I'm sure they'll have a big reaction.
Their reactions will be loud.
That's true. I'd like to see that.
I'd like to see that.
Next time...
Let's see who it is.
Or someone who depends on who you're talking to.
Okay, well, please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button.
Thank you very much.
I'll be waiting for you in the comments.
Who do you want us to surprise?
I'll be waiting.
Write it down.
Bye-bye!